Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is alright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Okay, I'll try one more time
And I have these really cool dreams
And I take a nap, but I've had like seven minutes today. I can't take any more naps
but
I'll try someone else the pressure is a little bit off because somebody else is streaming so
I guess have fun
Hopefully the souls will go over there. Well, not like hopefully they'll go over there bother anybody. They're probably like we probably like to get the people
Anyone has these little problems
I had a really weird dream part of the dream is like I
Was this some kind of dinner or something like that
Okay, I can't even sure because it really was my dream, but then I will just bother somebody so I can't see so
Let's say somebody came to that came to cars don't lie really the cars don't lie people do right right Ricky Ronnie
Cars don't lie people do
Hi, how are you all right hold on? Let me turn this fucker up. I don't feel like being on camera
You know while no pressure, right
Yeah, no pressure now like there's somebody else streaming. So it's like that pressures off tonight
Well, I mean I'm not being on camera. Oh, yeah, I
Don't feel yeah
Yeah, I know how it is to get some corn dogs and we're talking
And you eat that shit on camera people might like it take take pictures
Yeah
Some food fetishes
Just bring me the corn dogs themselves. We're gonna be fine. Yeah, that's fine. I miss this gum
I miss this gum
What's up with you, it's been a while.
Just chilling.
I came to talk about some things that may have been misconstrued and you hear things
To you directly and I you saw that it's me, right? You know, yeah, I know it is okay
okay
So as I break bread and I do I will wait
until
After I prayed to break the bread and eat but I I want to
Tell you
That I have no ill intentions and
Have nothing but you know if I poke fun, it's nothing but fun, you know
If other people are steering you in another direction
Maybe you know
Yeah, well, it's like he's never been it's like I don't remember like one time when you like you you like said anything to me or upset me or
Said anything bad like I never heard you say talk any shit about me on a show
I never you never called it like you and I might have offended you. I might have no
That's why you never did. Yeah, I understand when you might think that you but it's like yeah, you never did like
You know what like one time you were like
You're a mod one time and then you're like, I don't want to be a mod anymore. And I was like, okay. I'm not it wasn't personal, right?
I just you know, I kind of go crazy with the gay jokes and you know, I don't mean to offend you
Well, so I go crazy with the gay jokes. No, no, no, I think about the thing about my sexuality
Offends me. It's just like it's like basically people
Calling me things out of my name like, you know, the scammer or like oh, yeah, or like
You know, I just always care about his money money and dick
And I'm just like isn't it like a bad person then and then I got like like what's the biggest city backstage?
Wait, what did he say last night all he had to say last night was oh, you know, I was gonna let him on I was like
See, you know, see I'd like you. I don't have a problem with you. I'll like I'll have you on the show
Whatever then he starts going
well the problem is you enforce the rules for some people you don't force it for other people you
can't make your own rules it's youtube's rules and you know you know and so i was like okay well i
don't feel like talking about that tonight but as they also have you know and then he kept going on
and on about it i'm like well stop talking about that or i'm gonna ban you and he kept talking about
it still and so unfortunately i had to ban him and it's like i don't really care what he doesn't
say anymore because i've heard everything i've heard i've i had about enough times to have heard
Yeah, we get every every every negative thing you wanted to say every kind of kind of should talk to you want to say
I'd let him say and now he's just on a repeat loop about it
And so it's like why am I gonna put myself through that anymore? Like I don't understand why sake should come up
um, but
YouTube monetization
is strict and you are towing the line,
are you getting ads and getting donations?
You're maximizing your profit.
Right, and the thing about the ads too is that,
yeah, I can monetize the videos
and I can put ads in my old videos and things like that
and I do.
But when people say the n-word like he does like every time practically that instantly instantly when someone says that that puts a video on limited
unlimited monetization because
Advertisers don't want to be associated with that
And so I don't want to have to explain that every time because then people will just keep doing it to the screw of the monetization
But yeah, so that's that's a stress when he keeps doing that that screws up the monetization for maybe 11 hour shows
That takes the potential earning out of that video
Over the lifetime of the video, right? So that just takes money in my pocket. And is he donating money to like, you know
Compensate for that. No, he's never donated any is he wanting to promote his rumble stream every single time
Yes, and and he's wanting to like put me down and insult me every time. Yes. And so
Why do I keep always been gracious to promote streams?
Yes
Yeah, I even modded him at one time. I mean, I must have been insane, but I had him modded at one point
I don't know why you know, it's like I never I
The truth is is that I don't have time to hate anybody
I don't hate him, but I'm not gonna subject myself to being abused every night on the show like by him
And then it's like it just it takes on the whole mood
So I miss him done with it, you know and plus people and some people chatting in the thing
So tonight we had like some person came on like seven accounts
Talking the same shit. It probably was him or something. You know, it's like well, I
Sorry, I do that
To me
I have a bunch of scum a account
Well, don't but it's like the first okay company on with different named accounts tonight
But I but they think that the names were some of the same names because they just changed it to like put your
Screening or your your official channel. Yeah else comes in
So I have clown face scum a
it's me with the clown face and then
have the smiley face with the third eye yeah but it's stylized so somebody else
has cloned my shit and they jump around and they say weird shit and they try to
say that they're me but only him only that person in the chat and blackout
You know, who's who's this? This is you mean, you know, you me
Thank you. Hi, you me
Have the corn dogs. Yes. Yes. Hi
Hi, you me cat. Yeah. Can you put a smile?
Hi, how are you tonight? Oh
You're good. Good. I'm sorry. I left a little bit earlier like I came in
I was just I kind of got
I kind of got that a drain feeling again like I just was like I just was like right
I was about to fall asleep because I just like I get drained by some times of
Things people say and stuff like that. So I can't take another nap and then I'm back, but
Yeah
Thank you, but I'll try to be on for a while. This is camera
Are you someone from this beta?
See
I've been on beat us. Yes
Yeah
Yes, I'm as I'm beat is and and that's what other chats. I remember yeah, man. Oh
That's yeah
The friend friend of the show. Yeah
And I would hope that like, you know people that are like on this show are friends of the show because it's like
at least, like, you know, I care about the show and I wanted the show to be, like, a good,
good, happy, like, fun time and it's, like, people lately have been dragging me down a
little bit and, like, there's been a lot of, like, things said that aren't true about me
on other shows and...
Yeah, it's like I go on sometimes and we'll defend myself, but you know the last time I did that on one show
I came up and then it's like the guests started attacking me and I I
Didn't feel like anybody had my back and so I just left and it's like and
You know, I'm like now. I don't have like really the patience anymore to
Want to deal with deal with it and so I know I like had like, you know tons of people like, you know on a million times
We're not necessarily the nicest people in it or like people in the chat and stuff that I never
Would hide and I would just let them talk like that Fred Fred Alastair that every time I said Emma's name
I'm not allowed to say Emma's name. I'm not allowed. You know, oh, she's gonna tell on me a blow block
Hey dog, yo, hey, I was going psyche. Hi. How are you tonight?
I'm okay when the Fresno Bulldogs
Yes, come a I came up here to ask a me a question
Reason I came to ask a me scum a is it true about those allegations that?
You I'm not gonna say it, but it was read in the chat like you read it. Oh say it
No, no, I I'm not gonna hurt like his channel that that'll hurt psyche's channel. Well, I guess it's in another way
their way
The other way did you did you harm did you harm a woman or a child ever?
Have you have you been responsible for that ever?
Come in. Are you sure those charges charges on you?
Never have
There's charges. I've seen the paperwork. That's why I'm asking you. Oh, you have seen the paperwork. Yes, I have oh go get it
Well, it's on it's not it's on a discord. So
Can I go get it go get it? Okay, so I come back to get you two things at one time
Go get the proof take the picture and get it
Okay, scum. So I'm gonna get put your personal information your social security number your aggro
No, no, no, you don't say any of that you don't say any of that information
It's like, you know, basically if you read the police report, but it's that but I don't know I don't know
Report it's an incident report. It was an incident report. It was a 9-1-1 call that someone said
I don't know if it was a woman, you know, I don't want to say
Where I defended somebody that was
Okay, so you're aware of it. So you are aware of this. Okay. Okay. Now we're gonna
Yeah, but we don't know this story
house as a
Person that lives in the house. I had to control the person and say leave my residence
They weren't leaving so I had to initiate castle doctrine.
So I said, I am initiating my right to bear arms.
You will leave my residence or the police will be called and they were called immediately.
He left the residence and I said, there's no problem here, sir.
and that's it do you want to get into it more okay did you put hands on a female
yes or no never okay so why does that report skate that that that woman who
called 9-1-1 says that you put your hands on her forcefully and if you did
J dog and it's and if somebody is refusing to leave your house and it's like and you ask them to relieve your house peacefully
So you know at several times. I think you are allowed to use some kind of force to push them out of the house
Man or woman, you know, I think that you know just like not to hurt them
You want to get into my business more J?
No, I am not Arizona. Do you have the same laws? Do you abide by the same calm down scum calm down calm down?
No, calm down listen to me mother fucker
There's no need for that thumb. There's no need for that. You don't need to get you know
You don't need to get out of hand. You know, I'm not cussing. You know, I'm just asking you a simple question
Why don't you explain it to me?
Well, when shit has to happen you be a man and you stand up for your family in your house
Okay, well I understand we'll see now. I'm glad I got some clarification
You know, I wasn't trying to you know when you know
de-escalate the situation which we all have been trained to do as men
as civilized men, right, is to deescalate all departments
and military and law enforcement agencies had been trained.
I think the civilian population
needs a little training too.
Scummay, have you ever saw professional mental help
since these incidents have happened?
That's none of your business
Okay, scum because it sounds like you suffer from what I suffer from which is PTSD. I got that from the military
I do not know
What your PTSD is from? I don't know your whole story. I just saw a police report and I just want to ask you about it
I'm not trying to appear like a asshole
I don't know you that way. I've lived a lovely
Life J-Dog and I've given you chances to talk about it on another person's stream, actually
I'd like to talk about that
You talk about Beatles?
No, clumsy
Yeah, you cussed me out on clumsy so then you you took off you wouldn't even get a fit
We didn't even finish our conversation
You just you cussed me out and then you told me I was you were gonna beat me up if you found me and you got my
Docs and
Then you left
That was all that happened that night
Or you don't remember that either
Well, you know what it's like it seems like me there's a lot of police reports out there a citizen incidentary for obviously if there was some kind of like
Physical harm done to anybody there probably would have been some kind of arrest, right? And so there's
Yeah, they take that they think everyone statements so someone can make that statement and accuse that but if the police will say well
It doesn't really seem like either that was that was that wasn't either a necessary force or that was
It was maybe like
um elaborate on or you know um you know made up or something like that I think the policemen
yeah are best judgment with that right correct correct like he was never a rocket either he was
the
So, you know that I am clean, right? Yeah
That's what I'm saying. You weren't you were not arrested right fucking dick. I'm just asking you about an incident report
I'm asking you about an incident report
That's all I was asking you about and you're getting very defensive about that scum and I'm not cussing at you
You know, you're getting crazy with me. You know, I
Do we can okay? Well, so do I so do I but I'm not cussing at you. I'm not getting crazy with you from that
and we could talk about it till the fucking sun comes up because guess what it does late streams
so fucking you and your buddies can all jack off and discord
what buddies what buddies who i don't know what do you do i don't know what do you do with your
spare time weirdo weirdo by the way i mean you're looking up people on the internet that scared you
No, nobody nobody
No a blind man sitting in bed all day scared you I
Said I had your Docs because somebody said you lived in Fresno
And I was like, ooh, I can go off that.
And he reacted to it.
So, you know, you gave yourself away.
You know what, you know what,
mind games are played on these platforms, bro.
How long have you been here?
I'm serious.
You know how long I've been here.
No, I don't!
Yes, you do.
Am I am I your keeper? Yeah
It's somebody else can somebody else tell me how long you've been on this platform
Well, bye
You left okay, yes
anyways
Well, yeah, and it's like and that's like and again, it's like spring up like somebody doesn't like an incident report
There were there's no rest and anything that's really it's really obvious
That's kind of irrelevant and that kind of like, you know, I want you to be able to explain or explain yourself
I feel comfortable with that and it's so it's like I don't I hope some
Dinner well telling you that story just letting you know
You have a key cat there. Oh, yeah, that was my key. Shout out. It's the only paying gang
You guys
Hi, thank you. Thank you, man. How are you doing? He man she man. Oh, he man's he man she man now
He man she man. She man. Fuckin whatever dude. We're we're all together now
We're all together now all together now
all together now
Since you can't play the song. I'll just sing it. I
Want it. Can you want this? Yeah, this is good, huh?
This is like vanilla milkshake with coffee in it. Yeah
Very good. Yeah, but I drink I drink almost the whole thing and then I fell asleep
So it's like I think I'm like really tired or something. I don't know
I'm out of pot too. Maybe that's why
I've got a pot you see it and then it's like when I don't have it and then it's like I don't know
But uh, I'm thinking under a little bit of stress, but I'm better like I but I know scum so you're on scum is on
I know you're in some chats where I where you have everyone blocked
No, this account is cursed
This account has like over
accounts blocked and they can't be unblocked and I'm
trying desperately
To fix it, but honestly fucking who cares
Well, I say if you go through your Google and on Google if you go to your Google. No, I've done that. Yeah
Yeah, if you got to there should be a blocked accounts. You'll see like the 200 accounts
You can just unblock them if you want to unblock anybody
I gotta do it on another platform and and I gotta do it
Yeah, simultaneously kind of thing, but yeah, I I know what to do
But it doesn't matter
because
Nothing matters
Okay, I just want to make sure you know, you know that you know, you don't probably maybe might not see everybody in the chat
But my channel isn't really I'm not
monetized I
Mean it's aged
Yeah, if it's your channel, you can go into YouTube studio
But you have to go on YouTube studio on the web not through the app
And then you go to like the little wheel on the bottom and says like blocked accounts and then you can
That one's here
J-Dog's back
Okay, so in law enforcement, did you ever have to deal with any
ruffians
Did I order Jada? Oh Jada?
He was a military police officer, I believe so MP well shout out to the MP you got MP
I was never a cop. I was I was a military police or say a military police
They can be kind of iffy, but I agree
you are not doing the shitty uptight shit see the problem I have is like for
example when you call up the security forces or MPs or whoever is fucking you
flying
Cameras outside the fucking military installation here. Maybe you should
get a military guide to come out here and
And the dudes in the
Uh, fucking BMW not in the official fucking car. No, US government plates kind of shit. I wonder about national security. Now this was during Biden's administration. So who knows how they fixed it or not. Who knows? You know, I don't know politics wise.
I hope national security is good because
You know God forbid
Yeah, I
Live through 9-eleven. I would say most of us have I don't know Yumi's age
And she's also from another country, so I don't expect her to relate but yeah
No, it's me did 9-eleven trust me. Yeah, you remember you remember that? I mean I must have been let me see
I must have been it was 2001 so I must have been about 20 20 21 years old
Yeah, so I mean I watched the live it was
Impact if it didn't impact you live it definitely impacted your life somehow
Yeah, well, you know, it's like my dad was a military police officer in Korea, you know
I know this like a little bit different than a police officer
You know, it's like they my dad always like he always had his badge
You know, and you'd like to carry a gun and stuff like that. He always kind of fancied himself
In the police kind of thing, but you know, you know, he wasn't you're the business person, right?
But he was in Korea doing that and so I understand like you know, some will take it more seriously than other people and stuff like that
So I have police in my family
Yeah, it's me too. My uncle was the sergeant of this city. And so, yeah, so, you know, so I have police in my family too. And I do respect the police. And even though I've had a few run-ins, run-ins with the law and everything, I have been kind of like treated pretty fairly, I would say, most of the time, sometimes not. Sometimes they were kind of jerks, but, you know, they're a brotherhood and they kind of like see a lot of stuff. And so they're kind of not so sympathetic, sometimes empathetic.
No, I respect I did I was a snot when I was younger
But there's some times that I didn't deserve it and they were targeting me. So
There's an organ. What are you doing, bro?
I'm coming coffee not my pipe. Oh
You were I thought you were jacking off, bro. I was like, dude, what do you do it?
It looked I was like, well, are you fucking beating it right here online? Don't fucking do that, bro
You got your I don't think you would you wouldn't do that you wouldn't I just saw the arm motion
It's like yeah, I got scared for a moment, and I was like dude. Is he is he really doing this you
Military guys you guys you did some shit in boot camp man
You know, maybe it's a college thing. I didn't go to college. I'm what are you talking about go to?
Well, he's a fraternity sub to you. Do you ever you ever know? I got it. Thank you
Stuff I'm not into it and I watch gays thing confused
No, it's true. It's true. That's that's it shows. Yeah, the hazing. Yeah, it's the hazing. Yeah, exactly. He's right
I never got it. We we haze a little bit here, but it's lonely
mainly
Little jabs here and there. Yeah, I'm gonna say this if you could paper work everybody
Naturally and know everyone like J. God did
That would be the greatest, but that's not what we do.
We like everybody privacy.
But J-Dog, he did his homework and he found out one thing that I haven't been able to have anyone say.
Thank you J-Dog.
Well, I thought it was only fair because you have my Docs so and you get threatened to find me
Well, I know you can't beat me up, I know
I've been nonviolent since what 22 22 years old, right? I
Don't know how old you are. I'm 38
I know you are. I saw your paperwork. You got to train 39. You're turning 39, 1986.
1939. Yeah. 86. 86. 86 inches. 86. Yeah. 86 by the way. I don't know.
You got to you got to do your fucking math a little better, but okay 87 86 87 same things
Reagan baby get him right Reagan, baby. Okay, Reagan, baby
You say Reagan, baby, or you want to get close you say Reagan, baby, you know, I don't know
I had to start explaining my jokes around here because I think I understand shit
We don't understand you scum
He's been through, he's been through like a trauma and it's like, you know, it's like in a physical way too. And I'm sure it's frustrating. It's not easy. And it's like a, you know, he has to adapt. And it's not, it's not always easy. It's not easy being someone of that's completely like quote unquote, you know, normal, let alone someone that has had, you know, some kind of trauma and physical stuff happen.
And, you know, things can be triggers and things can bring back bad memories and set
people off sometimes.
You know, it's like, I think people, you know, people are able to control themselves
for the most part and, you know, not, like, lash out at other people and so, but, you
know, there might be misunderstandings and...
Yeah, like, you want to make sure that no, you know...
Sexually predators ever breathe again. So scum
The reason why we knew we're beefing in the first place
Really because I tried to be your friend scum. Do you remember when we first met? I try to be your friend
You came out my wires crossed all the time J dog. I am sure you picked that up
Yeah, I didn't your last got at me and you started cussing me out for no reason and so you have my dogs
Your military police officer is not anymore. I used to be I used to that your background you've picked up some things, right?
Yes, so please and
I begged you before
Right. I
Said please
Lay off
I mean, yeah, it's just gonna be barking
I can't do much help unless you want to send somebody to come shoot me
No, no, no, no, no and minecraft minecraft
No, no, no, no, no, I don't want nothing bad to happen to me scum. I like you
I wanted to be your friend. I just wanted to chill with you and hang out with you
That's all I ever wanted to do with you scum
Hello everyone
Yeah, okay. Thanks. I just thought of comes again. Well, I thought there's a great agreement for a second. I was like, bro
How are we all doing tonight? Yeah, well, it's like so we can get bastard. I mean, it's like
Yeah, we all want to like, you know give too much specific information about anybody
Especially like on a public platform like this if you do if you guys do want to like, you know
Talk about in private and you can probably talk about this stuff
But yeah, I don't want to have too much information like private information, you know shared about people
I sure of course have shared my birthday. I've shared my full name. I've shared my city and I'm sure and so I'm not surprised
You know, I've been docs and things like that and maybe
It's kind of a relief though because it's like instead of fearing I'm gonna be tossed. I've already been doxxed and it's like
Yeah, the worst has happened the worst has happened with that and so it's like, you know
There's like basically I don't have to worry about it anymore because well, it's done is done. So but uh
Okay, so yeah, oh he left so um there's some left
How's everyone doing how are you acid trip tonight? What's up? What's up with you?
I'm doing all right. Thank you. It's Sunday morning here. Maybe seven a.m. Just having a beer
You know
Nice. Oh, here we got ghosts coming in. Let's say I had a ghost
Hold on
You're
Hey, how are you?
Good. How are you?
Good. I'm okay doing better a little better. I'm just hanging in there
Um, nice. I was listening a little bit, huh?
Well, it's busy. I've been busy a couple days.
Busy? Or do you work in or something?
Cool. Yeah, I've taken up double, so.
Well, that's good. I mean, I've been okay.
Well, today I got my, I got this like little tool.
It's like a camera. See this, it's like a camera
and it goes inside your ear, right?
And
It's really cool, I'm not gonna show you guys what my inside of my ear looks like because it's a pretty disgusting
But it's like is
Harrier than I thought it would be but I know it's team saffron. I don't think I met you but Namaskar on do you know
Team saffron. I don't know it sounds like maybe you're from India or something
Um, Saffron, I know Saffron is popular in India.
Yeah, AstonChip, are you Indian or you're African?
I forgot, you're Somalian or Indian?
I'm Indian, I'm Indian here, like the same as that team Saffron.
Okay, yeah.
Are you Hindu or are you just the ethnicity?
I think, I don't really know too much because I was born in London, so I deal with UK stuff and that, but I think I'm Hindu, Gujarati.
I think it's the same Hindu and in Kudra is something like that. I think I have a I have a sister-in-law
You know for several years. She is her family is a
Indian origin, but they the family lived in South Africa and they lived under apartheid in South Africa where they were like second or third class citizens
And then they moved to America and started a liquor stores or things like that, you know, and so
But so I do have a kind of, I know, kind of similar, you know, ethnic Indians that are around the world.
My mom was at South Africa one holiday last month.
She was staying at a friend's house.
Yeah, I wonder how it's going over there in South Africa.
I just remember, you know, we actually had a, this girl.
I went over to South Africa during the apartheid and she was from my area basically, forgot her name exactly, but she went over there and she got murdered by a mob of angry people.
And so they started a foundation and then we had an exchange to come from South Africa and come to like conclude our school for several years.
But that yeah, that's cool. So yeah, so we got we're our world wide and I don't know our crucible goes
So that only if you want to share we're do you live in them? We're like for part of a part of the country
I've said it like a I've said it many times on your show. I'm sorry. I forgot
Okay, well we don't have to say it West Virginia West Virginia, okay
Yeah, we had a whole good. We had a whole discussion on that cat. So I'll say are you
But did you were you bored there? Do you have that because you don't have any kind of Virginia accent?
I would guess that you're maybe born like in the West, but
No, no, I was born there moved away
all the way up
Until like basically high school then I moved back but now no accent at all
I do be getting it especially when I'm like
If you're drinking a little bit, you know, like if you're found so many people you just
Tend like you tend to pick it up even though I you'd be like 40 years old and there's some words
But I love I love that accent, but now I don't have
Yeah, the southern axis
I grew up in the fucking
middle
In the middle middle of the country that they go hot like let me see what's in the middle like yeah smack dab
They like the dust bowl area
But what is the Kansas or something is that in your Kansas?
I'm trying to think of like the middle of the country
Not doing too good
Okay, yeah, let's see. Well, let's just like let's have a let's have a night. We can bring him a sig
I guess we've had requests for him to come out. What happened to the
What happened to the two people that were here? They leave that was J-Dog and
Yeah, they take they take off. Yeah
Are you gonna behave signal
I don't think he can hear you.
Every time he looks down, he's not going to behave.
If you look straight at the camera, when he first joined,
it means he's going to behave.
I didn't expect me to let him off.
He didn't like it.
Okay, he's already on thin ice and then he's going to decide to be annoying, okay?
So my fingers are already getting itchy, but let's see what is that?
I don't know, I mean Alice, Alice, I think Alice has done pretty much with the show.
I did get a request from somebody that I really care about that they wouldn't be
Well, I mean you can uh you care to uh talk about that at all or if you just like
because I know you probably don't
I guess it's different though because you probably don't even like him do you?
Yeah, I'm unfortunately
Unfortunately, I had the band sick again
He I gave I was gonna give him one more chance, you know, and then he comes up shit. I'm talking nonsense
So I banned him from the studio now, so
Yeah, that's it. I mean it's like I can't you know I was like okay one more time
I was I feel like I'm in a good mood and it comes up fucking shit
and so
So that's it.
So yeah, so I'm sorry if you like to sing
and you know, if he is on rumble, go visit his rumble
and you can go hang out with him there
without, you know, uninterrupted, right?
Okay, so team saffron, you're 45 minutes away,
45 kilometers away from the border of Pakistan
and South side, just after 100 kilometers
from the Thar desert begins,
your area is a green area due to agriculture,
lands and canals.
Okay, that sounds beautiful.
I know there's so much India that is beautiful.
It has maybe a little bit of a bad reputation sometimes, but I would love that's one of the places that would love to visit India
I would love to visit Italy Norway
where else
Norway, Sweden, Finland, the Nordic areas, and maybe some...
Pakistan is a very colorful place in India. There are colors and colors like it's different than the rest of India
They wear really colorful clothes and it's quite a fun place
Mm-hmm. Well, it sounds like I think Raja
didn't Raj mean King or something like that. And so it's like probably where there's a lot of royalty
around there or
so, yeah, one of them one of the
Some gorgeous areas Pakistan and the cashmere. Well, sounds beautiful. Thank you for coming here tonight. Nice to see you
I do I should have some new people coming here because I
started using these these hashtags on my
On my video and the hashtags, I think we'll make it easier for some people to search if they would like a tarot reading or things like that
I do have a new deck today called
Right here. This is called the combo list tick tarot five seven eight one
It's a cool deck if anyone would like a reason just I've got also my cat full spiders deck handy
I have my toxic. Let's let's get the toxic or the haters exposed deck out and then
I'll pull a few cards for everybody, but then if you'd like me to pull a particular card for anybody
Yeah, out of the haters deck. Yeah
I'll take the one
Okay. Wow. Wow. Like what is what you thought one part?
Okay. Oh, well, I don't know if I want to base it on three, but definitely one
But it will have every mean what you want. Okay. I mean cuz it's like
From that deck before so I don't know
Some of them are remit our remedies like it will give so it's like better to do a few cards
I think out of it so I'll pull three out of this one because some are yeah, yeah, good idea
Okay, perfect for me. Okay, there's turn these ones over, okay?
So haters exposed, so let's get for ghosts three cards
It's gonna be three good cards, I know
And this will
Hopefully it gives some information. Okay, so I got to the deck kind of a little bit upside down. Okay
Come through for girls, please
I always come this one says business rival and it says can't stand your grind or hustle and
so maybe somebody at work or or some kind of business rival is watching and they do not like
how much of a hard worker you are
and how you're doing pretty well,
but this one says get a dream catcher
to hang over your bed.
And so that might be a remedy.
There might be something when you're sleeping,
some negative stuff being sent,
and I think the dream catcher's a little hard.
That's a good card,
because I actually do have one, that's a good card.
Yeah.
If you have that, get it out, put it over your bed,
because that could be a simple remedy
for any kind of negative energy being sent towards you.
I think you have to believe in it too,
not just hang it up though.
Right, but it's like but even if like maybe just like we can like kind of choose our beliefs sometimes and it's like not kind of thing
It's like oh, I believe in it. It's like not some huge taking on some huge like you know dogma or anything
But it's like hey, this could like imagine it just like captures the negativity right and finally for ghosts. It says
Secretly jealous and hating on your romantic relationship. So I don't know if you are a romantic relationship
But if you are you might have some
Some ex-boyfriend of theirs or something is
It's not happy or it could be like a friend of yours
Yeah, let's say somebody that has affection for you or something like that
So I don't do you have a what do you still have that first card you mix it back up into the deck
Well, yeah, it's something about a business rival and it was just an eye looking but I can I can try
Well, I think I took that a different way because I think we can interpret this different. Yeah, yeah, sure
Sure, you mean is that whatever
Yeah, maybe that meant like
It's not even a business rival because I'm not even on YouTube or anything. Maybe that meant just like
I don't know. I don't know why I took it this way. It's like donating money, you know
Right, it could be which I do which I do by the way, let me explain myself
I do gladly and I don't have any kind of ill will towards that
I don't know why I got a hint of that on there, but now I do it
There's been people that actually talked shit to me off this
this channel on different channels and like
It's like like they've literally talked shit to me about it. It's like dude. I can be aware of the fuck
I won't first why I can be aware of fuck. I want my money
It's like like why are you worried about it? They're third of all like
They're like, oh could you because there was one dude? I forget his name. I'm and I don't even want to bring him up
This is gonna cause drama, but he's like what you you uh, you kicked me off or whatever
And I was like, you know what I won't do that again
Ever even if I donate money, I won't be getting it upset you
I it was all funny games like this is the reason why we pay money
But I was like I won't do it again. You know what? I haven't seen them up here since that so I don't know
Yeah, I mean it's a but that's a isn't it weird. It's like I would never think about going to somebody and say
Hey, why did you donate to this like it just doesn't come through my mind?
It's like it's not first of all, it's on my business second of all
I'm happy if any YouTube creator gets it. Even if I don't like them. It's like, you know, I believe I believe in like, you know
People are entertaining. They're providing a show and it's like if people like you why'd you buy a why'd you buy a chicken sandwich?
I mean, why'd you buy a chicken sandwich or why did you like it's my money? I can do whatever the fuck I want with it
right
And so it's basically if you hate the guy that's a different argument
We can have a debate about that
But if you're just talking about like the only reason I'm upset with you because you gave money
Well, you'd have to make the same the same logic if you go against like well
Do you hate charity like because I'm not saying this charity work with the same love that kind of applies
It's like you care about where my money is going so
It's more about I think it's more about it's more about they hate me
I mean they hate me
Yeah
Okay, let's take it. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah, and so it's like, you know, it's like I hear that under their shows too
Like oh, don't donate to him like what what what does he use the money for blah blah or he has money or blah blah?
It's like all these these these allegations and like misconstruing and people making assumptions and people really don't know anything about it
Like it's so it's like it's just like that's one of the things that big you're kidding me lately is like
people say like, you know boycott me or like or or or don't even boycott me just like go good go and
Go get on the air and and you know use them as much as you can and you know, he'll promote you
He'll let you promote yourself. He'll talk to you. He'll let you on the air
But yeah, but don't but don't don't give me anything don't you know, don't don't I'm compensating in any way
That's it was really fucked up
Way to think for so it's just that kind of bothers me that mindset of people thinking that they even have the right
So I give this is the best one and you all well to me
But you you might like this one too. They also said to me like
Do not donate on this panel, which I never had this problem, but do not donate this panel. It's not know the panel
He's doing whatever and I've literally literally the next second came over donate it and guess what we did
You open up the fuck you open up the panel and let those certain people join. It's like well prove you wrong
Yeah, maybe you just want me to pay you maybe you're using reverse psychology on me
Well, you know, it's like, I mean, that, I mean, that's fun.
I mean, it's like, I don't think they have good intentions out of it, but I think sometimes
even bad intentions, you know, misunderstood, can be turned into like, you know, it's like,
basically, maybe maybe it's only going to help me, you know, maybe that stuff only helps
me when like, people, people, people do see, oh, well, he's being hated on for like no
good reason.
And so I'm not going to, I'm not going to be like everybody else and just hate, hate
Other people do or because you know so-and-so does or who's mostly his his best friend is
You know laughing laughing at him and teasing him and saying, you know, you know
Constantly bringing up the biscuit or you know, whatever. It's like
Times psyche that I've literally
heard and I'm not saying anything but I've heard certain friends say something I've literally came over and been like hey
Open it up. Here's the money here have them on and then I've been like who wants to talk about
Well, that's really you that's literally what I'm talking about like who wants to have it. You know what they did
The first like what like a minute they talk about it then after that guess what they were all silent
It's like why were you running that mouth so much like?
No, they just like I think if they just like touch it. They're like prey on people's downfall
They like not see people succeed like they know they like to think they're doing better than someone
Wow, not true friends. That's what I think 20 minutes. I'm not mentioning names because I'm like those back
Oh, here we go. Maybe 30 minutes. That was backstage
visit what happened 30 minutes
My on the list. What were you doing? What were you doing all that time?
I was watching something. He put me on the shit list
Cuz you were watching something. We let you finish the episode and now you can join he holds grudges this guy
For me. I'm talking about me you I didn't see you backstage. I'm sorry. I'm like
Even shut a flare up. All right, let's start again. Hello. I got how are you tonight? How's everyone?
Hey guys, guys, hi, are you okay God? Like are you mad at me?
I'm not mad at you. He was he was drowning back here. I'm not mad at the sweetest guy I know.
That hair, that glasses, that white in the background. Who could be mad at that guy?
Oh guys by the way, so somebody was just backstage like they were last night and there is there's a hey
I need a hey I need a reading
Can you please I need to read anything to help and because of last night when I left the guy on and it was just you know
Tony and he was saying oh, you know, you know and we're and we're and we're and we're like and I and I ended it
So I said so this guy this guy Craig was backstage and he said can I get a tear reading life has been crazy lately and I said
Well, I said if you'd like a reading on the panel tonight, please send the $5 cash app because I don't know this person
And I don't want to end my show again and like, you know
I've already been on for an hour and I wanted to leave the hour and here's what he said
I'm not donating shit get fucked prune. And so you know what that means. Yeah, fuck them
It's like it was a little test. It was a little test. It was a little test to see how someone would react
I have no idea.
You could have kept him backstage.
You gave him one for free.
I wouldn't have done it.
But you could have gave him one for free.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll do a nice reading for you, but obviously that was Tony or somebody else right and it's like and so
You know, you can see how people react and so I wouldn't even want to do somebody
It's not like a year ago. I got accused of being Tony. That was the most disrespectful thing I could ever heard
Yeah, I know
You mean you want some cards or you want a few cards? I can give you that
Haters or I have a Kabbalah deck today, too. I just got this new Kabbalah deck. It's pretty cool with God or
scum or crucible ghosts or acid ship who would like a
Reading what's that? Oh, I would love a
Okay, you're welcome. Have a nice day. Have a nice night
like they're there. I mean, it's like, that's the thing. It's like, and if you don't like the tarot, it's like, you maybe you should find another show because this show is going to be more
Yeah, but it's basically not the best show if you're like if you don't like to tear
I mean, it's like you can at least like be pleasant and like sit there and just watch the people's readings
You know how it's like not that I have to read you
But I'd like at least like I'd like respect towards my art like craft whatever. Okay, so God, okay
The king of cups the king of cups. Okay. Yeah, you got a king and so the king of cups is all is like a very
He's very in control of his emotions like and maybe
He's matured into this state where it's like he's come into the kingly energy because you know when we're younger
We all we can like you know lose control of our emotions, but it seems like some kind of maturity and
Handle on in your emotions like a very good. Okay. What else we have we have only we have justice
Okay, we have there's the justice and just it has a sword right there, right?
I believe in scales even justice. Okay, yeah, there's a kingdom delivering justice and that you know
That's also I control my emotions and I'm big on justice
And everything's in the upright so far, and so that's a good sign, right? And finally, we have the moon. Okay, so the moon card is
There's something that's not to be revealed or won't be revealed yet
But it will be, you know, the moon goes through phases and things are revealed
But there could be some kind of dream state fantasy illusion at play
Covering up something, but it will be revealed the moon always is revealed. I'll pull a couple more
I'll give you a nice five cards. We're gone. Okay, then we have five five of swords. And so this is kind of like
The five of swords is kind of winning a competition. It may be
You see he has their swords down and they're kind of walking away sad right there
So maybe you what you want to know why they're walking away sad
Look you got their sword, right? No because they don't have my grace
Well, and then we finally we have the four pinnacles and the four pinnacles is like you got your your feet on the ground
Suddenly on the ground you've got your money on your mind and you've got you know
Penicle in your hand, too. And so you're like, you know, you're just daring
Someone to fuck with you, you know, it's like you're you're well grounded on the earth
Okay, so that looks like a pretty positive reading for you God. So as a whole, what would you say? I'm well grounded
Yeah, I would say that you know, you're definitely you're you're you're you're in a higher kind of energy
Do dealing with the justice and you know met measured emotion
There's still some secrets and stuff that might be revealed, but I have a different date
Okay, yeah, maybe a god would get you sound like you're now called like the likes of people first of all the king
Like like you like to drink a lot and then the second one where you live by the sword or die by the sword sir
You're walking away victorious after what I mean you cut down a lot of people sir
They're interpretation
It's okay. It's okay. God. He's just I think he's like having some fun
He's having some fun. Thank you. It was good. Thank you. You're welcome. You're welcome. Hi, Yumi
That was actually a good reading. Hey Vicky. You think cool
Yeah, Yumi got it in other cups. When does God get the reading out of the villain pack? Oh
Yeah, he doesn't like that villain deck for some reason
It's you it's you realistic realistic. I don't like the taros don't mix the tariffs
Well, it's like the thing about tarot is like there even the writer wake is not the deck. I mean, it's like yeah
It has major archetypes. It has the the general symbolism that is accepted
But you know that if you look at make individual text, there's there's there's archetypes there's messages and that
What I got a special announcement and I want to you do it on your on your
Channel here is next month. Actually, I've been working
on my own pack
Oh, you have
Well, I don't know if you like it kind of like a villain pack, but not really like a villain pack
But you know, you never know cuz you know you mean you mean I do I do have a new
I do have a new card that I created and it is the queen of wands
It's a queen of wands not doing to show it. It's a queen of wands and it's show that after
Okay, it's after Piranha, but she's not here. I do want to reveal it reveal it to her God. Don't know you don't have to man
Okay, I'll show it later. So when she gets here
What is it look at it though? Yeah, it's her pie. Do you know pie? Have you seen pie?
Pie that that's that big girl from Canada point one
God come on. God stop it. Well that girl from Canada. That's her. Yeah, I run. Yeah
She's an awesome person. Oh Canadian. She's at the Star Wars. Yeah. She is. Yeah. I like her
You might well. Yeah, I think she maybe she's a lovely person and uh
I talked a little bit about you know, I have a card for but is this one the chosen
The chill. Oh my gosh. I found these I found these old uh, these old acrobat things I had in the line
There's a guy his name is the chosen one his name is Juan something I used to watch him all the time because he
He had kind of this like a luminati type show. I haven't seen him in a long time
But he had because he had some pretty good discussion, but I have all these comic books like one is about
Let's see. What is it like one is about?
MK ultra one is about
Superhero thing and the other one is about me people just what's about it's about like I think some kind of like
You know controversial topic in history. I can't I can't open up now
But anyway, so I am working on the deck though a really cool deck
And I think you guys have seen like some of the pictures out of it and see
Yeah, it's okay. So poison VKG. You can advertise anything you want here. I'll say
You advertise your own show or if you have a friend like a personal friend
You can probably have to put their show you have to let a mod know in a mod will decide if it
You know, I'm not my psyche
Yeah, but I'm happy to like help people even people that don't like me or don't like to show I'm happy to
Believe in there. I believe in YouTube. I believe in like streamers. I think I consider other streamers as my colleagues
I don't have anything against anybody, but like I said
There is like this though, you know, so somebody
Syndicates a bunch of panel first people shows and so I'm on the list. You know beat is on the list
Good times on the list
Okay, but there's a lot of gate and then again Tommy James and a bunch of people are on there and I was like
Every like almost everybody else on the list like hates me and it's like
Wow, it's like I should be these just used to be my friends
It's like we all do kind of like a similar thing and it's like why
So all these people hate me like I mean all of them like uh, and it's kind of like a little bit sad sometimes
Well, I know it's like if you ever got to like set like
Well, go ahead. He asked you questions. Sorry. Yeah. Well, why did I think they hate me? It's because
Well, Tommy Jameson said we don't like you, you know cue blogger. I've had problems with
And then it's a good time. It's just like hates me calls me like so every kind of big
I'm slanderous drug addict, you know you can mention and then you know
It's just like it seems like a lot of people are not fans of me at least but it's like these are
Both themselves like that. Why do you take offense to that like you you got to be the odd ban out
Some of them do but it seems like they're they like like each other like they're always like oh
I love like they're all sending each other love notes and love letters and stuff like that and then it's like and
And then it's like I'm piece of garbage and it's like
Let me let me tell you what it is you don't do what they do that's the problem
You don't do what I do so you take offense to it and you you get
You get emotionally impaired about it sometimes
Well, I'm very sensitive like that's part of like my astrology even is like I'm very
Even though I can be emotionally detached at times with my Aquarius
This isn't a comedic fucking podcast and you can understand why he gets upset right God. Yeah, but he sticks out ghost
That's the thing just because he's not like that. Well. Yeah, he gets upset like if I mean I would feel the same way if I felt like that
Well, the thing is he doesn't do it. He doesn't he doesn't do it
We do he doesn't do what you do. You know what he means? He wants to sit up here
He wants to be positive. He wants to have a positive
Which is understand there's nothing wrong with that. He also makes some
There's nothing wrong. He takes he takes a little eye if the argument is like he takes up too seriously
Is that the argument?
No, he he wants to he wants to be friends with these people
But they want oh, yeah, that's that's true
I want him to be like them and he's not willing to be
That you know what God? Yeah, but then again, then again, I am we're colleagues though
It's like we are in the same like if anybody then these people like we do similar things
We have and we have panels on YouTube where we have the panel verse right and it's like there's not too many people that do this
Streaming our thing our community your colleagues from still throw you in the dirt for if they can get above you on the views
They'll throw you in the dirt. You know they will
Yeah, I really, comparatively, I get way more views than some of them, and less views than some of them, so I'm not the best, but I'm not the worst.
But um, but it's like even like the people that have more views hate me the people that have less views hate me
It's just like it seems like it's kind of universal and it's like I don't I'm not trying to be competition
I'm trying to I want to help eat all of them and all most of them are banned on my chat now
like a lot of them are because they come in and like been really
Cruel to me and it's like I'm not a cool person like
I'm gonna say you're not a bad person you're just like you take I think God if I'm not trying to make your argument for you
He's saying that, you know, you take it too serious.
Like people are, you know, people are being funny and stuff.
And then also on the other aspect of it is like,
you want to be everyone's friend,
which they'll act friendly to you
until it benefits them not to you.
And they'll fucking like,
they have no care in the world.
I mean, it's YouTube.
That hurts.
I think if I explain that correctly,
I don't know if I did, but.
That was okay
I'm on the right track and it's kind of hard to discuss like you know a little bit
But it's like yeah, you're on the right track with this
Well, why don't you try going over to their panels and be rude them like you think they are to you? Yeah?
It's like because I don't have that in my heart
It's like I don't like like what would I be rude about like it's like I like all I have is how they treat me
I don't really well don't be malicious with it. Don't be malicious. Let's do it in a fun way
Yeah, let's say we'll see how we'll see how long I last with our panel though if they won't last long you won't
Yeah, but trying to see nice of a guy
You'll come immediately if I say anything that is like construed is like anything slightly negative or passive aggressive
I'll be immediately kicked off when it's like people can straight up tell me to my face like I'm a piece of kick shit
And like I don't know will you be tickles?
I'll get kicked off
I'm sure I will
Like and I'm not I'm not trying to go to use like you know, I love you do that
But I feel like you just you kind of just leave I don't know if you mean I obviously not adversity any of this
But you kind of just leave there's been a couple times you just left because you were hurt, you know, I'm saying which is okay
I'm not saying something wrong with that
but
I'm not attacking I don't go attacking I come on positive and like and like when I like you know
I'll be like hey if anyone wants to do it all give someone a reading or blah blah blah or you know
I just try to be positive and offer
You know offer something and it's just like I don't know if they think I'm like being straight or I
Don't know God would you agree with me? Like maybe be a little bit less a sensitive which I know it's hard to do
I'm just saying I'm just saying it in general. Maybe be a little bit less
Such that maybe learn how to just debate in a tiny bit and then just have fun with it regardless
You know, I think that would benefit you. I mean, I really do and I'm not
There's been negativity that since the beginning kind of thrown at me by some people right and it's like and I've been able to
Go with it and stuff like that because now it's getting to the point where it's like I just like people that I don't even like
I remember like maybe we're much at like a few months ago. They're saying oh
I would never know there again because of people say oh, they said this about him. They said this about him
Oh, I'm not going to have to pay to get on the panel blah blah
And then it's just like people do something that's common knowledge that are absolutely lies and slander and it's like
It's upsetting like having being misrepresented like I really do care about people
I don't care all about money and stuff like that, but at the same time, I do have to survive, I have to live, and I want to be doing this full time, you know, um, and so if I was doing something full time, it's like, if people can't see something full time, unless they're able to survive in the world, right, and it's like, I can't.
I've paid to join the panel, but also I've joined a lot of fucking times for free, a free open panel. I've joined a lot of times for that.
it's like you can only be you man you can't be who people want you to be
you can only be who you are yeah exactly yeah yeah
but it's like you try to be everybody you're not going to be anybody
but it's like I try but I hit myself and I and I get treated like that so it's like
there's something like wrong with me like but I'm so I'm free it's okay to god would you agree
it's okay to like I don't want to say troll because that's not the necessary the word that I want to
I mean, I don't know what else were to use it. Maybe you guys can explain it better for me
But it's like it's okay to like troll a little bit
It's okay to like it's okay to make fun of people. It's okay
Yeah, but big fun of people that it's like hey first of all it's like yeah
It's like we're talking about Howard Stern and something out and the difference between Howard Stern
trolling the WAC pack and Howard Stern goof and in company whatever
Goofing on the waxer and though that dude was kind of out of line the whole time kind of I mean my right
But yeah, he changed a little bit, but it's like but it's still he would mainly goof on people and behind the scenes
He would be you know kind and he had he understood that they were part of
Yeah, so he's like he wouldn't in you would like you know, and you would never really sometimes, you know
He'd make fun of like, you know physical
know maybe differences they had or something but it wasn't it just didn't seem like it was in such a
I like I want to keep things funny and not cruel if it makes sense
It's like no worries. I don't think I get offended that people talk about me being in a wheelchair for like seven years. I don't care
Yeah, I mean it never bothered me it never bothered me
But if I was up here and somebody talked about it, you would get offended and you'd kick them off probably, right?
Well, if they said it in a certain way like you know, I even I put it in the song
But it was like in a good nature
I mean personally I don't think the only time he's ever kicked me was when they broke TOS
I don't think he's ever got offended. I mean, and I've been up here a while
So I don't know maybe I'm just wrong when you
Many times
Was I I don't know if I was there what I think I'm pretty sure I paid to get you kicked off God honestly
I'm pretty sure you did. I don't think you paid to kick me off
Well, yeah, well, I like talking to you, but I probably did pay to kick you off though at some point
it was two people that came to kick me off
Well guys, you know Tom Tom flash is here and then poison BKG makes the point Tom flash
Didn't you pee bomb this panel when Rusty or JT were on the panel? Don't let him join. Don't let him
Then he was in he was in
Beta's chat under the same name joined a person ever I've literally been psyched like we'll literally ended 30 times in one day
Because it's been so many porn bombs like that. Oh my god
Yeah, that's not Tom flash. That's that's somebody else
Well, but who is like
Who would make a fake Tom flash though?
And it's like and also I heard that he said stuff about me on his show to trust it
Because they want you to go to war with Tom flash over here
He hates JT and the woman rusty, okay, but it's like that but only my show doesn't do anything
He doesn't do anything to JT or rusty if you form bombs my show that only hurts my show
Yeah, that's like you dumb fuck. Hey, you lose either way. Haha. You fucking lose either way. Good logic. I
Hate flash up JT. So I'm gonna bomb fucking psyche. I'm a hurry channel. I don't know. How do you win?
Okay, I don't know
Where's that logic
Okay, he just wants to my book my shows to get more views. He won't say I don't understand because I haven't talked
I've just seen him talking, you know, I don't know maybe it's not the right person
I've seen him talking to talking other chats about oh, I'm trying to take it down a show
Come up here and tell you personally if he has to he won't play it down
But yeah, yeah, he has been on my show and I just like let me let me run it with him
he's not going to go about it, let me go
he's not backstage, he's not backstage
Tom is a funny psycho, alright
but once he gets really psycho, you're going to feel it
that's what they want, they want him over here going psycho
well that's concerning
what do you mean by really psycho
like beyond psycho
is he going to break the OS
is he going to break the OS sir
he can't be described
He's gonna break it. Let him come up here. I'll fuck every one break every fucking wall
Then then why the fuck are you making an argument for him if he's gonna break you less?
What's your argument God?
because you kind of hurt and psyched him because you wish like you do this shit though you do all time
Oh, maybe not, but you know these people are they got here's my fucking one at the question
Are they gonna break to us? Do you have a problem? Yes, I'm the same question. Do you have a problem or does that?
Does blackface break to us yes or no
I don't know probably does I probably does to consider some kind of racial
Talking to him. Let me handle this. Okay. Does it break to us? It could or could I don't know does it? Yes
I knew yes. No does it or does it not? No
Do you know if I fucking put my face black right now as a white boy
And I fucking I was on psyche's panel. I wouldn't get canceled. Yes or no psyche would cancel you
But I don't think YouTube would cancel you so therefore it would be so therefore it would be against to us
So why the fuck would psyche let anybody up here? That's gonna break the OS. That's did I just say that?
Well, yeah
Like there's a guy in the background. There's a there's a guy named
Reviler red that was on last night. He's his face with painted red and then he kept saying weird obscure things about
Hebrews or do you think he's learning Hebrew and stuff like that
But then he has this word written on his arm that means like death and it's a kind of like in a secure way
It's like by the way, it's like yeah, I'll just leave because like there's people in the comments
They're just gonna join because they know I'm gonna debate them and they won't
They want to prove a point which I'm down to debate them, but I I know for a fact these people
They like to break the OS, but if you want me to stay off looking all right with anyone we can do it guys
It's anybody know who bloomers UK is bloomers UK. Yeah, I know
Okay, let her up. Okay. One second. I'm just gonna put my banner better. Oh, it's her though. You will put our faith in God
Hello
Hi, how are you doing?
I'm good. I don't know if that was the real Tom flash or not. I know and where have you been?
No, it's you. I'll say it. It makes you
Yeah, you're interesting on the show. Yeah, I don't know if you know this Tom flash guy or do you have a problem with them?
Or what's going on here? This one said he doesn't like you. He's someone
Wasn't this a porn bomb? That was it was actually a CP bomb that night. And so that's like even like really really bad
Yeah
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
Whoever is pretending to be Tom Flash is not Tom Flash, okay?
So I don't know who it is because I haven't been around, but whoever is bombing under
his name or coming in the chat or using his avatar is not him.
He doesn't come here.
He's been on the show. He's been on the show. Okay, one time. What was his name again? I'm sorry. What was his name?
Tom flash
Flash what the fuck do you think we're gonna think he doesn't?
He doesn't go to other panels. He doesn't but yeah, he has talked about YouTube channel
But he runs a YouTube channel. What the fuck do you think it's come flash with a name meaning flash flash
Feeling it's because of assholes like this
Shut the fuck up and let me talk. I'm talking to you
You're talking to me. This is my business
Shut your fucking me and Tom flash all about that. So go ahead
This is why your channel is failing and why you're having
Assholes like this
Can't even have a conversation up here, but you better come respectful we never
Psyche about Tom flash. Oh, well, you should have said that it's no
It's an open panel, correct?
It's an open panel!
It's open meaning any...
You should shut the fuck up!
You should shut the fuck up actually.
This is why you don't come here.
Yeah, be gone, bitch.
I'm a very, I want to talk to you.
You're a very retarded person.
Most of the time, I want to talk to you.
If you're stupid to have the conversation.
Because I don't hang out.
You want to talk to Psyche at this panel.
You might as well just ask the whole reason why I stopped coming here.
It's because of dudes like Samann or who I don't even know who these guys are.
Yeah, and then when I talk to you, you're fucking like, yes.
Just fucking talk over me.
Pay to kick me off panels and shit like that. I don't like me to pay. Would you like me to pay ma'am?
We can be respectful. It's an open panel. It's psyche's panel. You said pay
What do you want to go? You want to go? You want to go dollars a dollar? We can do it
You want to go dollars a dollar?
Why does your case have fucking control here and let me talk to you pat
Okay
They go ahead wanted to know I'll give you you want to know or do you not want to know I wouldn't tell me
He was up here and you say okay at the time that he was actually up here
He stood up in his boxers, but he didn't flip his dick out flop his dick out or anything like that
I don't know if that's what you're referring to but
No, it was it was actually after it was not the night. He was on it was like somebody with his name trying to come on and then they
Oh, okay, and a weird CT on the channel
I don't know I just been listening listening to you the past couple days you've been listening
You kind of kind of can I can I crash out?
Can you get this fucker to stop talking over me?
Hey, you go
No, I'll give her 20 bucks to kick me off the fucking panel. Fuck it. I'll give you
So I can come here
I've been streaming for fucking years. I don't put up with this shit
That's why I don't fucking like you
You you stick up for somebody who likes to flash I don't it's like he's never flash
He's a good host
It's good panel to be over here. Stay assembly. You've been crying for days about how fucked up it is or whatever. I don't have anything against you.
Alright, well let's fucking run that bitch. How am I crying?
Alright, get rid of him.
So make-
Or I will-
You're not gonna get rid of me.
Yeah, yeah.
Did you can leave? You're not gonna get rid of me. Trust me.
Alright, well then you deserve whatever. You deserve whatever.
That's a good argument.
I don't like this shit. I don't put up with this shit.
You know what, it's like y'all wait for a little bit, I'm just looking out the window.
Yeah, why don't you?
Send your fucking business.
Hang around, man.
Hang around.
Just hang around for a minute.
I don't fucking put up with people talking over these shit.
Man, there's no need to leave, man.
You can just chill out and hang around, God.
Just let her talk for a minute
Okay, so who left yeah, go ahead
Anyway, so, you know, it's a situation with me that that happened a couple weeks ago or whatever
I don't anticipate it happening anymore, but I'm not here. So the guy stalking me. I've been in court with him
It's a big fiasco
And I don't blame you because you didn't know any of that and I can't stop him from going anywhere
Just like I can't stop you me coming up here or acid trip from coming up here
Your panel, but you didn't know him
You didn't know him he purposely came here because I was that's what that's the reason why I haven't been around
Because I don't want him fucking following me here and making a big
Scene which is what he did and he and he recorded it so then he can play it back on his channel for you know
content
or whatever
Anyway, it's not a big deal. I'm sorry about that. I have
I get pissed off. I don't like people talking over me. I guess you could call me arrogant or something
You know, I'm not in the mood right now. Normally, I
With that certain individual is extremely rough on me
You know if you go to my channel, which you don't go to my channel if you were to go to my channel
You'd see like the past ten days of him
Ranching about me for hours and hours and hours on end. It's terrible
He wishes death on me threatens to kill me all sorts of shit, you know, it's not real fun
So I'm not in like the greatest mood about it. I
Got I got you. I'm the same way I get a little bit
you know a little bit I have enough
Can I take the time to apologize to
Axe real quick because I feel bad
Is that okay?
Yeah I'm not in the grade
Yeah I know
I know
And let me take the time to apologize
Absolutely nobody
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about
You're a person bullshit. I haven't left
This is an asshole like all those other
And I call you nothing I'm saying
It's like that too, but
I can't I'm gonna viewers you didn't you just like didn't you just like brag about how man was one of them
And I can't remember you don't know what the fuck you're talking about straight up. You want to run it. Let's run it
You don't know what you're even left to let you know
Right now you wouldn't be talking to me like that I can
Let's all get along. Let's have a conversation
Let's do a smoke a peace pipe
Listen when you crash out you gotta make it known you gotta make it known if you're gonna have a good crash out
You're crashing up. Nobody gives a fucking you crash out
Straight up
Nobody cares. Why are you laughing?
God, why are you laughing? There's a guy in the chat named Jack booby
What is that? What is that?
What is that?
So I logic you
Okay, oh, yeah, I'm gonna remember you know for me. It doesn't make you an intelligent man. Let me tell you that
Go ahead
Shit on the fucking panel cuz you're talking over me. Okay. All right
I
Gave you the chance to talk and all you had to say
I don't deal with little punks like you. That's not what you deal with
Be quiet
I'll make the most irritating fucking noises and drive you right to fuck off here. Well, you're retarded and you shouldn't be on the panel
Artic noises and make some more friends here if you're if you're retarded, I can't help it
Would you like to be my friend? I mean I can probably help you do ma'am. You're the only person here that I don't
Yumi Kat and Gaudi are all my friends. We might not be best friends, but we've all known each other at least four years
Yeah, we all know one retarded friend. I have a retarded friend too. Would you like to be my retarded friend as well?
You're the odd man out. You are.
You don't have to slug me. You're talking about talking shit about psyche. You've got me fucked up.
I didn't talk shit about psyche.
You ain't never going to talk shit about psyche. You ain't never going to do anything.
What are you going to do to me if I do?
I'm going to out-debate you. You're...
Oh, debate me about what?
I'm an out debate, you know mental
What's the subject? Let's get this let's get to the subject
But I'm not gonna do it
Talking about shitty pay to get me kicked out, go ahead.
Dude, how do you a streamer?
I do not stream.
I told you this in the first fucking 10 minutes of this.
I couldn't read your name.
I hear who I was trying to remember the name of.
Oh, yeah.
You're too hard down the conversation.
How am I a piece of shit?
Okay, well, that's a good claim.
The burden of proof is on you.
How am I a piece of shit?
Go ahead.
Cuz you're an asshole you talk over everybody. Oh my how am I not so you you're another you're you're fucking ass-licker
You're looking like he's asked to
So the burden is on you, and all you have to say is I'm an ass-licker. Go ahead and do that.
Yeah, cuz you're paying the money. Go ahead.
You're paying money. Do you pay his rent this year?
Run it. Go ahead.
Did you pay his rent?
Off you want to be button here for him God's but buddy
Drop his entire fucking red to get you off this fucking panel. Go ahead and drop it bitch. Go ahead
Drop it
You're punk I'm done with this
You're a lot of people when you're stupid and you don't know how to debate.
You own the panel. You own it.
Once I realized you were too stupid to have debate, I actually tried to talk to you.
You're too stupid to do that.
What are we debating about?
Because you think you're full of shit.
I have this many powers. I do this.
How am I full of shit?
I can drop some money to get
Because you think you're hot shit
Oh, I have this many followers, which you lied about that
You lied about it you fucking lied about it. You don't have that many followers
You don't have that many viewers. You don't the fuck you're talking about. We'll never step up
You're promoting my channel. I keep my straight up. So yeah, you did
Talking about yes, you did bang the gong
Thought be gone
Go forth and thought no more you're
Was a changing
God go forth
Critical of you, but that finger yours man
I'm saving it
What does that even mean
We're finna give you a proper crash out here
It's you have nothing to talk about. Okay, go ahead
What's your argument?
I'm gonna do a little back you up. I'll put you on your tongue. I love this
I hit my drama quota for the night
Some of the dum-dums we bumper ahead here
I'm not allowed over there. I'm not even allowed to talk. You're talking about let's run that bitch dog
Yeah, what do you mean? Why right? You know why now? You know, we're gonna be really mad now
Haven't broadcast that yet. Yeah, it's like he's got a ghost here now. Yeah, we run this shit different way
I didn't share that one. We don't like recarts
I don't care straight up defensive. We don't like reparts
It's taking Andy really at this hat. How'd you get too stupid? No, it's not him. It's like you run this
Yeah, we don't like yeah, let's run this bitch. This is your life. What ghost ghost ghost what?
This is your life. What is that argument? It's your life. How is that an argument?
Is this your life? If you don't know what the argument is, maybe you should just jump the fuck out of it.
And this is the people that were coming at psyche. Hey, psyche. These were the people that were coming at you.
Just dreamer coming at my boys like he fuck you you fuckers keep it at the conversation come number like you
What do you do wrong? He's running the YouTube panel. He's doing good for himself. He's so good dreamer looks good
Why won't anybody answer me?
Are you why does it matter? What are you gonna join my fucking stream dumb fucking whore? I don't want you
I have a girlfriend. Are you a streamer? I have a girlfriend. Please ma'am. I have a girlfriend. Are you a streamer?
But psyche got you back. Oh
So you
Screaming it's like we're scrapping in the bathroom together. I have psychies back. That's my brother
Yeah, this is your whole life, huh?
It's like he's my brother. Why do you have a problem?
No, we literally have the same father. I mean that I guess that you
Okay, God is your father. Yeah, God father. He's got father
You don't the fuck you're talking about make the argument or fuck off bitch. I'm tired of hearing about you
I don't have to pay to kick you off
I don't wanna have to pay for your silver card. You're so small.
Are you going for a piss or something?
3,000!
You got three thousand three thousand in what now I got at least three
Three and a half thousand right now, and then I'll pay four
You want to run it run it are you gonna shut you're gonna suck
I'm just looking at what I need to get to me, ain't I?
I've got a suitcase full of money for you here, right?
See?
Man, stop laughing.
I'm tumbling up.
Right, let's get the stuff up.
I think it's in here.
I'm not too sure.
I'll shut up talking.
I don't need any help.
I'm trying to help you out.
Respect your elders.
All right, we're too retired to have to come you too stupid to have to come give me back my robe and my lipstick motherfucker
Maybe you should just leave and take your followers with you. We don't maybe I should maybe I shouldn't maybe you maybe you should we
Don't want them. You me
You me
You know, I'm done with that. She needs to leave
Now I have to pay money for this
You I mean
Can I just somebody else I already have money built up
Money and then I'll go to it. I don't care. I'm asking him a question real quick
Are you chucking a pat? Are you chucking a pat?
You me! You me!
Psyche!
You mean that to me?
Are you chucking a pat? Are you chucking a pat?
What his name's psyche is not in horror. He loves being dumb fucks. I could hide away
Well, you're going you're going listen here you're going either way either I have money built up or I'm paying for you
You're gone
I won't do it. I won't do it. You don't like that. I won't do it. I promise you. I won't do it
You stroke your load because you get a pat on the head
You don't like Tara you get a pat on the head from
Hey, uh, psych you get a card for acid
No
It's always you can't be a free reading
Have you kept have you kept track of things goes
I think that might have
You have one left or I think you might have one left. Yeah, yeah, well, you know what fuck it
Well, I think I have three left, but if I have one left and yeah kicker then fuck it
I agree with it. I think I have three left though, but fuck it. I agree one left. We'll call it cool
One what
Actually, you better leave. I got one left credit. You know what ghost if you buy five again
You have to leave
I have to keep
You know, there's a goal. Yeah, there's a goal
We'll go on the bathroom and jerk your worm because you kicked off x for 25
Regardless kicker off be gone with her. All right good. Thank you, but we have
You know what? I agree with it because I agree with it. Then we're fair then I thought I had two more
Can we meet this goal?
Hey, and if I didn't, hey
Listen, it's your money. Do whatever you want to. I'm fair. Ghost. Ghost. We're trying to meet a goal here
What's up, brother?
I'll do the goal. I'll hit the goals. It's only five dollars times five. That's 25 dollars
I'll do it when I'll get back from small don't do 25 do at least 20
That's somebody else do the five at a time because the minimums fiber at times
So I'm saying is don't do the whole thing by yourself
I'll do a couple and that might give some people some motivation.
Oh, it's real, it's fucking real.
The man's got a goal there, isn't it?
You need the certain guy, the one who's got a goal.
I'll say we still have the guy out who's behind it now to put a stream up.
So, like, how long was that?
Was that, like, five minutes with that all night?
That is, you can decide to bring it back if you'd like.
You can bring it back.
But it's all night unless I choose to bring it back.
Yes, yes, but you banned it. Did you know I'd I agree
They are you paid to ban them busy shit. Oh, you had credit
She could have game up you bring a little bit nice marriage. You fucking talk to her if you buy five of those do you get one free?
Yeah, yeah
This ain't the gas station where you go up. I won't get one free. It's like yeah, get a sandwich
This isn't master Patel's castle
I do I do have I do have something to play one second. I think that you will enjoy but it's this is it a ghost song
Is it a US?
You will be in the next one. You'll be the next one
The next one
No, no, no, you're gonna be the next one
You know what there's another ghost in this one. Oh
What's up with her microphone? It's not working
And do I hate you up there and she could talk she's crashing out. She doesn't sort of work
Yeah, fuck me started you weren't I read your lips
You said no, oh, you read my lips. You know, you are you are in a song. You're in welcome to the madness
Play it. Okay. I'll play it in the crash out. This is welcome to the madness
And Ghost is in like the second version here, one second.
It's a welcome to the madness.
Oh, here it is, right here.
Welcome to the madness.
It's 9pm, lights up, mics, hot chaos in the stream.
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boo slashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting goned Alex taking flight
It's wild it's wrong and we do it every night page got them simping hearts in the chat
no filter all facts yo all facts yo yo michael drops a line gong not tonight alex
tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways someone's got a
fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirt
slipping down low oops she says with a wink that's the whole show size half a
to play one hand on the mute other letting it spray it's a circus a riot a beautiful mess one
wrong word and we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob
smashing on cam chat losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight it's while
it's wrong and we do it every night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time
Next verse. I didn't hear ghost one time. Okay. I have to do it again. It's not again. It's next
There you go, yeah, you know that theater from bless bottle one of some time you mix me up in the crash
That was it
To the right
Okay, there you go see if you just yelling it goes with a bottle of wine
I didn't hear Gary you mentioned me a beat are you this is
I'm gonna put you in it. I'm gonna make a ghost song actually
I'm gonna do a whole ghost song that my favorite guy goes. I'm feeling crash out
I mean, we're gonna make it tonight goes. I'll do it right now and you guys can talk, okay?
I'll go make this one. Okay. I'll be right back
No, fuck you already talk to you. You get your own song. Wow
That's awesome dude. You really made the big time. You made the big time ghost man. Congratulations
Wow, how'd you do it? How do you do it? How do you do it? I'm cool. What the fuck you want to talk about?
I want to talk about how cool you are
Like how he how he did you become one of the most loved people on YouTube
Money anything else
What money
You bought your way in fucking retard. You asked me the question how they become one of the love
One of the most loved people on YouTube
But you don't have to fuck you're talking about you're obviously stupid. Oh, I don't know what I'm talking about
I just said you're one of the most loved people on YouTube. How do I not know what I'm talking about?
How I'm part of the number zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero one percent
How am I the most loved even thought go ahead and explain what you don't think you're the most loved
Every way you go people talk about you. What are you talking about? They love no, sir. No, sir
I could name four panels that you're loved at least four panels. Okay. Go ahead and name it. Yeah
Go ahead beat it every time you go and beat this panel. She fuck no, I know no
That's one. That's not that's not true. Don't summer summer's panel. She fucking loves that's not true. Don't fuck
That's two three
Of course psyche psyche loves you that's three right there. Yes. All right
You want me to give you one you want to continue negative two you got
You're like a what do you mean you don't know what TPP means
You're too stupid to have the conversation man. Goose. What are you trying to say dude? You're not loved?
All the people yeah, fuck you and them the people's podcast PPP. Yeah, fuck you and them low self-esteem
How do I have low self-esteem go ahead and explain it to me because you don't feel like you're loved
How would I be loved go ahead and explain it to me if you making your argument you win ghost ghost listen
Go ahead. You have thinking about it a little bit. Yeah, listen. Stop talking and listen
Accept your flowers. All right, I'm accepting shit boy. You keep people off the panel every day. All right
What did I do? They come back on my pain? I don't have a panel come back and what I don't have a panel
What do they say? What do they say when you come back?
Oh, I like ghosts. I like ghosts. He's cool. He's cool. I like ghosts. He's cool. This is after they got kicked out.
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about, sir. This is after you pay to have them kicked out. Oh, ghosts is cool. I like ghosts.
You have no idea what you're talking about. Oh, ghosts is so cool. There's many a people that won't say that.
That's called love
Being loved now you're trying to come in let's run it. Let's run run but here you're fucking one of the most loved people
I know
By the way
I'll fuck you.
What's up, I'm on that shit.
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with shit?
Do
the
I don't know it's like device. It's like it's like like the AI's gone gone rogue
Can someone block that person it's just getting ridiculous, please please please
I'll do it. Is there a mod in the chat as soon as a mod in the chest. I'll leave right now. I can handle it for you
Okay, but your thoughts coming up so wait wait a second. Wait a second. You can say it's activating a virus. Oh, yeah
Thank God loves my song
Who are you?
Oh, cool. I'm a tattoo brother. I'll be right back
Shit
I think you do the hearts for ghosts
is to make you feel upset is deciphering that make you feel sad that I got the hearts
he's deciphering the code
I'm talking to you
you're not going to run away from this by the way guy because you do this like you fuck these
who are you
these people but
yeah I'm a ghost
I'm over here whatever you want to call me
who?
bitch you know who the fuck I am
I don't know actually
that's me the same fucking question
you asked me it four times
If I say I'm the same person four times you asked me four more times. Hey
I'm the same person. I don't like your panel
Unless you're too. It's not my panel you retard
I'll send a crash out and I know you're gonna get me
Jack Booby
What the fuck are you talking about Jack Boobie?
Boobie Lee, Jack Boobie Lee, he's friend Jack Boobie, what the fuck, Boobie Lee
I'm gonna go
Cannibals and I've never forgotten working for my laptop, so I'll try on the phone
So I'm gonna go up one of the goals by
He's recorded we can hit this goal or what?
Well, no bitch, you're not donating are you?
Well, I'm waiting for somebody to donate
Well, you want us to give me and you will go back and forth. I say anything about you
Somebody's donating. I mean, I'm down to do it might as well
Hey, look the 65 people in the chat somebody has to donate. Yeah, at least somebody at least somebody's gonna donate or join
I mean 65 people. Let's go. I mean, it'd be illogical for me to say that like that would be
I mean 65 people. Let's go
But we were on the journey one of the like don't mean
To retard the answer okay, I'll answer for you trying to show
Yeah, I was until we got to this that moment. Yeah, I was the I don't know what they're donating for Shay
Just the goal you said a goal
We see that circle
Like that brother goes because are you ready?
You ready? I'm down. Let's run one. I want you
Have your soul I have your song ready. Hold on. Oh
God's gonna love this one. Let's fuck. I'll be right back
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. No. All right, pause it pause it pause it. Okay. Okay
I go ahead. I'm gonna hear that. I'm still when you back
No, when are you but psyche? Don't let him do that. When are you back?
I'm taking a piss. Do you mind?
No, you're gonna listen to my
Now you're gonna listen to my song
You're doing that you're doing on purpose of this effect me do listen to the song
Yeah, okay ready the fucking nation or not, but you're being disrespectful you're
No, he's being straight. No, give me one second psyche. Give me one second, please. He's being disrespectful fuck
Fuck it. Yeah, fuck it. Let's run it. Fuck them. Yeah, I
Don't like it already
Do you like it girl?
You should apologize you are
Yeah
my face turns blue your funny as hell yeah it's always a blast these moments
we're making you your last thing to go you're one of a kind with your big heart
and mischief and your quickfire mind
Oh, I fuckin' like you.
Hey, shh, I'm playing my song.
I see. I'm so good for you.
Oh.
Jack Booby.
That's a poem.
Yeah!
I'm foreign in here
God damn what a good song
Guitar let's go
You know hey ma'am
My song playing with
That's a great song
It's great song. Oh
I put that shit off, born in, Yerick!
Come on, Dan, you got it?
Yeah, I am.
Stop ruining my song, shut up!
Yerick?
Awesome, Gretchen.
You want to run ones? Yeah? You want to run ones?
Alright, what do you want to talk about, Fimo?
I'll play my song.
No, no, no, no, no, you didn't have nowhere to play.
Yeah, yeah, play my song.
Go ahead and say what you were going to say.
No, fuck you and fuck your song.
What are you saying, Fimo?
Best song ever.
Yeah!
You want to run it?
I'm down to run one.
Play that shit.
I'll fuck you and fuck your song sir. We're gonna play it right now straight up
No, fuck you and fuck you want me to repeat it again. Fuck you and fuck your song sir
You won't say that when you hear it
Fuck you
Hold on a second. I'm sucker from the back here
That's gonna crash the fuck out. I don't know why these bitches are coming here where I was talking to psyche here
Who are you all you got a bump? I'm talking to I don't know what you guys got a bump into I'm talking psyche yet
Who are you?
Dokes
Who?
Are you retarded?
Who are you? Are you stupid?
Huh? You're a tart. You're too stupid to understand what names mean. Are you okay?
Yeah, good one good one good one psyche let's run this motherfucker you're it
Ain't nobody gonna focus like a year
Don't wherever you want. I'm here year
You mean why are you so close to the camera?
And who wants to fight like you? Let's fucking run it. Are you a little beta anybody who wants to run it out running with anyone?
Do stupid to have the conversation
You want to run it or not?
That's the bait. All right. Let's just debate. You want to debate? Let's have a real the fucking debate. I'm down. What's running? God join on them
It has ghosts money really help the channel yes or no
Well, we have to enjoy so I feel on that. But yes, I will agree with that
So psyche mean him's agreeing to a debate we're gonna go one-to-one, but you're here so I would agree with that
Okay, okay. Let's play the song real quick is the gaudy song and then I'll let you guys
Come on, let me play it. We've got it's really good. It's really good my real song
Yeah, it's your real song. I played it for you, Gotti, before you liked it.
Okay, here we go.
Out of New York came a storm on wheels
Rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper
Pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner said psyche
I'm bored, had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screaming on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back
Then crashed my show like a heart attack
Gotti made man, troking my...
But they're still my friends
Yeah, love, you got it
Till the bitter end we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
He's God with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief brought spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones
They all jumped in cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but nah, I like my circus
I love this mess every troll is just a test stop and that's got you
absurd and free but deep down you got
We troll, but we friends, forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat, then held it down
You got layers, like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade, a heart made of ice
rice so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of chaos welcome to
psych you brought the drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're
the one got it yeah you crazy but your family now rolling through fire still
taking a bow no matter the madness no matter the weather but we stick together
My show tomorrow
That was beautiful dude, it is a sweet song. That's the second time I heard that that was great
That's way better than ghost song
Way better, dude, and I'd have to pay $1,000 for it either
Oh
Well you paid an extra security for my
You see ghosts, that's what real friendship is you write a song about me because he cares
You know, I care about goes I care about goes to oh, yeah. Yeah, of course. Yeah. Yeah, sure
About all of you. Hey guys. Do you like that song? Okay
They love that song
This is a song good not bad. It was a nice song. I think it was a great song
I mean, I'm gonna make songs that I haven't I have nice thing to say about everybody I do and it's like and then it's like
you know me with the
mixed with the AI and
You know, it's like it's a lot. I get a lot of help. I get a lot of help that it is like I do like put a lot of
The con I put the content, you know, it's like I know the content and then it's like
I'm able to
Tell the AI what to do and it basically is working for me. Okay
There you go. The beat
Same though, it always seems like the same beat with the songs not just yours
Everybody everybody. Yeah, it's improving. I think they go after like there are some certain like, you know, but it's improving
they have chat
CPC 5 and
No, it'll just get better and better. It'll get more unique and that kind of thing can't be like too much
Camera goes off in the afternoon. Yeah
It was a real vampire. Yeah, we know
Your wife
You see you. Yeah, we don't leave me. Don't leave please
Come back. Yeah, we come back
See you. Yeah, we come back. You mean you may come back
Baby gotta hold on me. Don't don't leave me. I was wrong. You mean you don't leave me
And I just can't leave without you
You like that guy he's about
Is that me all alone?
to be like that.
Yeah, I mean, I have some pot,
but it's like a pretty good pot.
Guess it's over.
Okay, well, bye, bye everybody.
I guess it's over too.
Well, whatever.
How about I like getting the Speedos
and like, you know, hang out with you guys?
Anybody still wanna hang out with me?
I know, I'm like the,
one of the lesser draws of this show.
I got a cough now.
It is slow.
I don't wanna take a drama for the sake of drama.
There's no drama, then it's good
because it's like there was gonna be lulls
and then the drama comes back
and we only use drama all the time.
Not, yeah, just chill.
Most Speedos, okay, HK says most Speedos, okay.
Well, I'd have to put them on anyway.
I don't know, might be slightly.
Okay, let me see.
I'm just trying to find my lighter.
Anyway, I said I'd stay, I said I'd stay until 1 a.m.
It's my final hour here.
We had two hours, eight minutes.
And I'll stay until 1 a.m. or else,
if there's a $5 donation, I will stay until 3 a.m. plus.
Yeah, I guess it's super chat system, but it you can also if you send it you can send it all cash up
And then I'll take or you know one person can send it. I mean, I'll I'll I can
I'll do it
It doesn't have to meet the goal, but it is kind of fun when the goal is like met because all this confetti comes down, but
Why what why what?
You know just to have more time hang out what hang out longer. I'll get a little energized me a little bit
But uh, no no pressure
Okay, yeah, goodbye Indonesia Wi-Fi. Oh, yeah, why is it it adds in your names? It's because
It changed the show it changed your names to your actual three names or your channel name or something like that
Yeah, but why is that your photo that's you
Never mind that but why do they change it? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Why do they change it to the names?
Why why they because I don't know why they did it, but they change it
It's like we actually have like the channel name
Which is like what like that's what would come up before the channel name
So it was a psyche awakens tarot because we just chat you have to start a channel, right?
So there's a channel name
But then there's just like your screen name and so it changes to the screen name
Which is like the at and so it's like my name got changed to at psyche awakens. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I know it changed
I have no I don't know but you know YouTube's gonna go through a big change soon on the August 14th
Which is in four days they will begin to do an age verification system
I'm assuming AI and it's like if you have like you know
They're gonna analyze your behavior like web behavior and people that like you know watch Pokemon and stuff like even if they're adults
They're gonna ask them to a to verify their age and then
and some people think it's a big privacy thing because they think oh well now we
don't have our IDs because you have to say this for your driver's license but they also say you
can just show a regular photo of yourself kind of like the uh the uh the t-app i don't know if
you know about the t-app you're gonna happen i'm not showing shit so that's it well then
then then they'll can't they'll close your account yeah and well you can i would say you
could just probably use like somebody else's photo but i don't know for sure like i don't know how
Yeah, but it's like I don't know like the AI might be like, you know, really good or something like that
I'm wondering but
Yeah, they're also doing something. I mean in England they just pass some kind of Childhood Protection Act, which is like they say you can't
Use like a VPN and you have to and you have to do the age thing and so they're bringing America
America proactively
And I don't know how much it is about or how it's actually protecting anybody or anything
It seems like it's just a way to identify everybody
and like
They are setting down the VPN access in England and probably gonna do that in America too. So
I know it's interesting. We'll see what happens, but you know, I think some people yeah that some people
Also, what's going on with the they're having an AI takeover for the moderation of channels
And so it's kind of that's going to be scary because it's like I mean
Do you have to ask it to do it or you know it doesn't it doesn't automatically it will start doing it
And it's kind of like gonna be like tick tock where tick tock has the all and so if it like tick tock notices
What you say like it analyzes like I because I've had like about 10 or 12 maybe more streams restricted on tick tock
And it says, because I directed people off the platform,
which is just me saying, hey, I'm also on YouTube.
OK, then it will say, oh, I'm promoting something else,
or I'm like, and then for smoking cigarettes
several times on the panel.
Like, they will make it for adults only.
Emma was actually kicked off of TikTok for like,
she said she had three different things.
I don't know if they're still doing the same thing
of kicking people off so easily, because I haven't seen that.
But uh like up for me like I haven't said oh you have a warning you have like one strike or anything
I bet I just I just keep getting my streams
Restricted which just means they won't like advertise and they won't be it
For kids and then they push all these fucking new
Yeah safety measures, but it's not for kids. It's just not yeah information and shit exactly exactly in that in the guys
But whenever you say it's for it's for kids or something like that
You can't really argue with people are you gonna argue it? Yeah, no, it's for the kid
You know, it's like that's what you know
There's always this class of the oh think about the children and so that's why we have you can't like you know
Everyone has to get card at the liquor store and everyone has to you know
part of the movie theater
Ayo, it's like, it's, you know, it's for the children. Oh, that's why they, you notice that every couple years, uh, that, oh, there was a big hack today. Uh, 250 million accounts were hacked by somebody and blah, blah, blah, and then all the information gets out. Yeah, fuck that bullshit.
Yeah, well, it messes up.
Well, yeah, but it's also like also like, you know, people can hire hackers and everything to do those stuff
They're the dark web, but there's like a lot of there's also the all these devices
Like there's a lot of devices that are like supposed to be like, you know
To make our lives easier like there's a device that you can run all your wireless
remotes and stuff
But then someone comes in with bad intentions and plays that device secretly and they all of a sudden they have controlled your air condition or that control
You know your your TV and your and so they can put anything out if they want and or I don't I don't know
You know different things like so, uh, yeah, oh here's goes back
We heard about the one that hacked the baby monitor and then like talking to the baby
Yeah, that was creepy. I mean how creepy is that? Holy shit, man. It's terrifying terrifying. People are sick. Yeah
People are sick and it's like and yeah, or people like talking on baby. Yeah, I saw that before like
But it also has some of these things like a lot of the ghosts stuff like not not ghost
Crucible ghosts are talking about like hauntings and stuff like that
There's like little tells that it's like fake because I understand tells you know what a tell is Goddy
Yeah
Okay, yeah, so there's tells and it's like that's how I can like decode a lot of the news
And it's like some people when they talk about this stuff
They sound crazy, but I could like talk to you privately and like show you how it's not crazy like I can you know
I I know it well enough to know it's real, you know, it's like it's it would be too
It would either be like life is just a purely a dream
and it's all symbolic and that kind of stuff,
or it's not the biggest coincidence in the world.
Those are not true.
There's no such thing as coincidence, I don't even think.
And then I just know maybe some inside information
that is available actually to everybody,
but there's so much information out there
that people don't know what to look for kind of thing.
And I've just been directed
But I've just been directed in the right right way where I understand and I know you understand
That's why I can like kind of discuss it and maybe the audience understands you you like it here on YouTube
I like it here, too. I'm still awake. I'll be awake for I've been sleeping all day actually
I slept probably more naps today than I've taken in my life
Like I took like seven naps and they were good naps where I was like dreaming like having like these really good
Vivid dreams and I feel better now and I still have another coffee. But first I might drink too
I just had a big coffee
Apagato, do you like Apagato Gotti? Are you a coffee guy? I don't drink coffee. Oh, you don't okay?
You don't like caffeine or no?
Coke zero only. I don't drink anything else. They have caffeine in that. I don't even know. I don't think so
Zero it sounds like zero caffeine zero sugar. It's definitely zero sugar, but I don't know about the caffeine
Hmm doesn't keep me awake. That's for sure. So my mom is like
Very sensitive to caffeine and so she's like she's strict decaf. Hey, you mean
That you know, hi, how are you?
I hate the Wi-Fi look on and off look it's a week. It's really low Wi-Fi
low
I'm really excited I'll be able to hi. How are you? I'll be able to this month of course get the computer
I think I'm gonna go for maybe a mini PC because I think I'm thinking I'm really good at maybe
There's many pieces are really cool. I can have it kind of out here without being so big
They perform really well actually I just like I just maybe won't be able to focus so much on gaming
But I'm still thinking about like because I really do want to do the VR
If I can find a way to do the gaming PC with a VR,
but also want to get a new vacuum,
I want to get maybe the standalone VR headset.
And I'll really be able to improve the show.
Like, I'll be able to run the show from a monitor
on this table right here,
and basically improve the streaming.
I'll be able to share stuff on my screen,
because there is stuff I do want to share
that I know is not copyrighted and stuff like that,
then I'll be able to.
Also, it'll just be it'll just be better the show's gonna get really good
And you can think I'm ghost because ghost did donate so much said it's like, you know
He was I was finally able to get this PC, which I've really really wanted so
So thank you. Can you can you do that thing where?
You can put a chicken on your head like if we if we gave money you can put a chicken on your head
Or you know, I thought I could I learned how to hypnotize the chicken. I know how to hypnotize the chicken
You just look into its eyes. Yeah
No, you basically, you know, you you pet it real slowly and like you can eventually get it to turn upside down in your arms
And I will just like lay in your lay in your arms like a baby
Go to sleep. Yeah, you hypnotize them. Well, they're awake, but you can hypnotize it. Has anybody ever hypnotized a
Chicken here. I've hypnotized a chicken. What are you gonna do if you put the sleep?
Oh, you just cuddle with it a little bit.
Oh, you cuddle with it, Jesus.
Yeah.
Chickens are sweet.
Actually, they're sweet.
They're sweet birds.
And they're really cool, crazy birds.
Like, I like chickens a lot.
And then they smell good.
They smell good.
Yeah, actually, the Martha Stewart got me into, like, you know, my mom raises chickens and stuff like that, you know, gets fresh eggs, but Martha Stewart showed this catalog where you can order, like, chickens, like, these exotic chickens with, like, and you can order the eggs and stuff, and they come in different, like, some of them lay different colored eggs, like, Easter eggs, they look like Easter eggs, they lay like, actually, like, pastel colored eggs, and they're a really beautiful shape, they're so exotic, it's pretty amazing, but my mom doesn't even slaughter, actually.
you know eight pigs were born or seven pigs were born um last year and then one of the people
wanted to buy it for a luau and she would not um she was she would not allow that so
oh she won't sell pigs for that
No, no, no luau because you don't think they they slaughtered the pig for the luau. I mean, it's it's
The pig didn't look great to me. I didn't touch it. I like ball. I wouldn't eat the luau milk pork
We use we saw actually we used to go to so we see you to go to Kona village would like every few years like when I was a kid or every
Couple years for Thanksgiving. We would go to Kona village, you know on Kona Island in Hawaii
It was really fun little resort there and they would have a luau. I just remembered that, you know
they would have the luau kind of in private it was more kind of a they would not let the tourists kind of watch it but they would
They didn't have pictures of it
They showed and they're basically slaughtering the pig and then they bury the pig in the ground and cook it in the ground
Yeah, and then they slice it up. It is the best pork. It's a serious. It's delicious pork
It's traditional. I saw but when I started it looked like it was all like um
no pulled pork looks it was all brown yeah it was yeah this kind of brown
it's very tender it's it's tender it's like yeah if you like pork i mean you would like it but yeah
it was exciting it was outside there were bugs around i said fucking i'm not touching that yeah
well i i mean i just i enjoyed that but i'm kind of adventurous when it comes to like food i've
been to thailand i've been actually i was a vegetarian in thailand but i still would eat like very strange
This is I used to be adventurous not anymore. What food not a fucking round
Okay, I had experience you had rabbit. I had rabbit years ago and then I had a rabbit
I said fuck it. I'm not eating rabbit anymore. Then yeah, I used you know, I love it's a curry goat
I
See I wouldn't eat goat because I'm a capricorn and I like I love goat so much
But I have seen in Africa with the word how they prepare a goat and they have like the goats heads in like the market
Like what that's with the eyes still in them. Oh my god. That's so much. Yeah, that's how they do in Africa
I mean that yeah, go maybe you're making Jamaican or something else like that type of drink. Oh, that's the good shit
Okay, I've never I've never had go I don't think I would eat go I bet I do like lamb and I just ate lamb today
I had a lamb. Yeah, that was great. I had a lamb Euro. Actually there's one yesterday one today
And man, was it good.
It was like just this tender lamb
and it had like a little bit of the yogurt sauce
and it had lettuce and tomato and some like,
the yogurt sauce was kind of cheesy
and in a pita, little pita wrap
and there was a couple of them
and also with the Turkish coffee.
We do lamb for Easter usually
then so we get the big leg of lamb, right?
So I got a slot of that thing in the sink.
You don't slaughter it you don't slaughter yourself the lamb you know what I mean cut it up
I got to cut the fat off. Oh, okay, okay like that. I got to get the meat off the bone
He's just water a slaughter. Then you cut that lamb up you fucking put in the bowl with the onions and the wine
It comes out so fucking good, you know the taste is like fucking amazing
Have you heard of Philippes?
I don't know, you're not in California, you're in New York.
But have you heard of Philippes?
Philippes is where they have the original French chip sandwich.
That's where they invented it.
It's in downtown Los Angeles.
My dad used to be there.
Well, the French dip.
I've heard of the French dip.
It's called Felipe's or Felipe's and it's like we used to go when we were kids and they have like saw dust on the floor
And they have these waitresses that have probably worked there for like 40 years and are these little cute outfits
You go up to the counter and order and they like put everything on a tray and give you the tray and you sit down like
You kind of like communal benches in there and it's like, you know, it's like running downtown LA and it's like I used to love love
Getting lamb sandwiches. Also, they have these purple pickled eggs. Oh, so good. I've seen those
Yeah, I know what you're talking about. They look gross
They're delicious. No these hot. They're the bright purple and I said they're just taste like they taste like a pickled egg
You know, it's just I never I was never big on a hard-boiled egg. So I never got into that
Yeah, well, I really recommend if you guys are interested in that kind of food like take up Felipe's downtown Los Angeles
You can also walk across the street. There's Alvaro Street, which is like the first Mexican street in the in the country
Hey, jingle. How are you real dingle?
Everyone has their real names out on the yeah, I hope that too many people don't have their actual real names
They might freak out, but yeah Frank Frank. Hey Steve. It's Frank here from a show
Hey, Michelle Frank Frank with you. I don't see any of these people. Hold on. Is that Kim? Hey, Kim. How you doing?
Nobody's here. They're not here
Hey guys, by the way, my show's failing or there's 40 people in chat right now at midnight last night
There was like 65. Well, there were 65 people earlier than last night at 3 a.m.
There is like 55 people so I'm I'm fine with my numbers also has been a successful financial month on YouTube and
You know through the through everything else and so I'm I'm happy with my progress
I think I'm doing okay. You know, I'm not gonna let people get me down. I know worry, dude. You're doing all right
I think I'm doing okay. I'm doing okay. It's just like I just wish that uh people like you know
I feel like very misunderstood, you know, but maybe that's how it's always been like I just like people don't do me
If people don't believe that I'm me like my personality like this is me like I've shown you the good bad
The ugly on this show like I've been like in my I've been I've cried on the show
I've like you know laughed and laughed hardest as an ever laughed at my life on this show when flirty diamond did the somersault
It's like we accept you for you who you are man. We don't care about your failings or whatever you
You don't
No, no, I'm saying that you're like we like everybody and it's like it's not it's like you you don't and
Some like a lot of people here don't like I feel like so many great people here
And I haven't had many trolls in the shit the troll I didn't have today was like the same person
And you know over and over and like seven accounts and stuff like that obviously and so it's like maybe I don't even have that
Many trolls it's just like the ones I do have like our you know super trolls that it's like, you know
I have super super anti troll powers or you know just from like
I told a little bit too, but it's like I troll where it's not and sometimes I like to troll the trolls, right?
It's like
But I really don't have a bad heart and it's like I really don't wish anybody harm or you know
No, you're you're forgiving person. That's it. That's what that's your superpower. You forgive people
Yeah, but
You don't let things go though. That's the problem. You know, you don't really let things go you carry it with you still, right?
But it's like and it's like other people are kind of similar to because you know
Vita is still mad about like what happened months ago with somebody and it's like that that that one thing snowballed
But to everything else and it's like and she won't get over that one thing and that was like, you know
It seems like she won't let that go and it's like I know sometimes sometimes things
We can't let things go because they're so like it seems so severe to us
But it wasn't like me that said that to her and it wasn't like her that said some of the stuff to me and so
Like we should I think it's like I always told her there's people are going to be turning kind of trying to like
Tear us apart and it's like it feels like she got suckered into that like finally like I mean it's like
You know, it's like you can only go so long people saying something so much until it starts having an effect and it's like
I never met anybody harm. I don't know. Hey Vicki. How are you?
So I don't want to love people from afar
that I don't want to love from afar.
Like I want to love some people up close
and like, you know, have them in my life
and be in communication.
Some people I do need to love from afar
and like not talk to as much and like limit my interaction
because they've been toxic and had bad intentions
at times that it's hard for me to trust sometimes.
But it's like not certain people
that it's like we shouldn't have a problem.
It's just other people came between the relationship.
And then it's like and then kind of like poisons your mind against me or I don't know it's like because it's like
Having a lot of people say the same thing
A lot of people are like sheep and they like to follow whatever else is saying and so you know
Spike let me give you a quick example. Let me give you a quick example
You know how I like to uh troll people and you call it being rude and stuff like that
You know how I like to like have fun
All right, right to you it might be like oh god. He's very rude. He's very rude to my guests at the same time
It's not it's not being malicious from my my
Let me let me just preface it with on the other end like from your point of view it becomes not not trolling
But you become judgmental where you where you throw on
you throw on the fact that you're saying that I'm being rude to guests they
it's only rude because they don't know me right okay well they don't they don't
know you but it's like you okay so first of all I understand but okay we're
talking about what because I've had you you told other guests and that's fine I've
never had a problem because most like a lot of the guests are trolls and so it's
like you know it's fine to do it to each other but I had on a lady that is like
took a lot of courage to start her channel, put herself out there, someone with, you know,
the same insecurities maybe all human beings have, but, you know, she's got great stories to tell,
she's got good energy, and she doesn't mean maliciousness to anybody. And it's like, and so I
want to kind of protect some people, like, you know, especially like, you know, she's a little bit
older lady too, and I want to not use this universe, and I don't want to scare her away and think that
like trying to put her in a situation or something like that, and I want to be extra...
Protective of certain people and so it was that I totally understand that I totally understand you want to like in your mind
You want to guess that you could relate to on a different level have serious conversations with you want to relate talk about tarot
Whatever, that's fine, and you kicking me off panel. That's fine, too
But it's when you start
Labeling me as oh God, he's fucking rude
Take his fucking
Why are you guys because that I was feeling protective of my friend and she had already been attacked all right
Ray J JT the elves LD came up and even trolls her and like you know people are just kind of it and friends
But you forget what you forget one important thing. I'm your fucking friend, too
Yeah, I know you're my friend and it's like but I can get pissed off of my friend
Sometimes you know, I'll give you back the wrench. It's like not about the wrench, but it's like, you know, I just want
You know, I would do the same thing to you if someone was going after you like an unfair way or a cruel way
Like and I felt like that was kind of unfair and cruel to her
Because it's like you don't have the relationship with her yet
We're you didn't get to like try to know her and like, you know
At least at least be nice to somebody the first time you meet them be cordial and then it's like and then maybe you can like, you know
Troll tease a little bit. I would like I would like, you know, I prefer you get to you know
I just want you to troll everyone arbitrarily just because it's fun to troll. She's a sweet lady
She's an interesting woman. She's uh, you know
She's she shares stories about how she was homeless at one point and she was a street musician and
Someone came and had to take a crap in her guitar case and she had her cane
Yeah, she had a can she just like swatted his ass and I hit him really hard with this
I think there's funny stories that you would like you would like, you know
And, you know, it's not for the same reasons, not for the same reason.
You think that's funny that I did that?
Well, I don't think it's very funny, but you know, I think it's funny that she like.
Yeah, is that Alex? Okay. Well, so I I don't know, you know, I think she has some interesting story
But it all I'm saying is like don't just jump down people's throats
And also it's like, you know, if I have a guest it's like one of my rules is very respectful to the guests
And I know it's like, you know, that's why I do it. I take me off
You don't have to be so you don't have to get so mad about it, dude
That's the thing. I know baby me piss you piss me off. You piss me off, dude
There's no need to get pissed off is what I'm saying, dude. It's not that serious
Okay, well, I know but it's like at that at that night that night I was under I was already annoyed because other people are already done it
It's like and then she is getting upset and offended and it's like and I don't and I was having a great conversation
I don't want her to think I'm having people up here to ambush her or anything, which I'm not doing but it's like
Yeah, I think it is good training for
Because I think, you know, but she already has the show. I mean, she gets trolled already. And so, you know, and I know it's maybe worse over here, but, you know, it's good that she sees how bad it can get and stuff like that.
I just don't want her to feel...
You know like you know like I like I put her in a bad situation or something like that or you know
I don't I don't want anything bad me negativity
I've already had people like just drop me because they think oh well your friends are weird your friends are bad
I had people just drop me because of my friends and it's like but I love my friends
I understand like they are a lot of them are trolls and
You know, but as long they're not trolls to me, but I just want to make sure like you know
One time that's what it was see we're here all the time. She only comes one time
She she comes quite often
But you know a lot of times she comes in the chat and the chat's not friendly or the panel's not friendly
And she'd be like well, it's not a good time for me to be here, but and she's also busy
She has a show too and I want and I want her to be able to promote her show here and meet some new friends
But I don't want you know just trolls coming over there and making her life hell like you know like because sometimes
Feel like I've been on some shats that that have brought fools here that have tried to make my life hell
And it's like and then I think it's a lot of them
I've gone and left at this point because it's like you know
You can only show me for so long before I will start to start banning people and stuff. So
Am I okay Alex? I don't know. I'm just hanging in there Alex. So, you know, you have a check on them a while you too
Now you're calling you're making fun of you me and stuff like you know, I want to have you on the
Oh gosh, can you get the eight? Yeah, you you can't get it away. Jamie. They changed it. Okay. They changed it
So I don't know I don't maybe if you go over there and do it
But okay guys so 15 minutes left. I guess nobody wanted to continue the show let out
I mean, I would but yeah, but I mean we only have a few minutes left because nobody wanted to
Nobody not one person gave five bucks. Wow. No, no
Well, I'm sorry.
Oh, no, but that's the thing.
It's like, not only that, it's like nobody's donating anymore
because people are saying, I'm a grifter, I'm a scam artist,
or I'm unfair.
It's like ghosts.
That's why I really appreciate ghosts.
And it's like, I'm pleased about people
that are harassing ghosts and calling them names
and stuff like that.
Like, don't do that.
It's like, ghosts is actually one person
that actually still cares about me.
It's like, but yeah, most people have just abandoned me.
So anyway, yeah, no, but nobody
It's like, you know, and I think I am providing the entertainment stuff and I wanted to say you know
I've been here for like three hours, or I'll be over three like three hours tonight
But it is hard when it's like nobody
They don't want to give a dollar, you know for several days in a row and stuff. So but no, it's like that's all your it's all your
No
Don't know just like you think one person, but I'm just saying it's not it's not your fault
I've been slandered. I understand if you think negative things about me like I don't deserve it and blah blah blah blah
You know, it's like that's just that over and over and it's like that's the new narrative now
And so I know I just have to deal with it
Yeah, they'll come they'll come they'll come if people wanted more of the show tonight
Hold on I'll let Sam and up if you want more of the show tonight
You still can you have like 15 minutes left
But you know, I'm not getting my hopes up because you know, I know I'm just being slandered so much that nobody
Cares anymore. So let me just hold the banner. Hold on. Okay. Sorry
Nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do